Tufts University Website Collection UA203
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student organizations web crawls, 2011 -- 2021; UA203.002; 575 Web sites
  - Fungal Futures SMFA - Instagram, 2020 -- 2021; UA203.000603; Fungal Futures Mushroom Club; 1 Web sites
  - Girls in STEM - Facebook, 2020 December 16; UA203.000604; Girls in STEM; 1 Web sites
  - Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000605; Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs; 1 Web sites
  - Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000606; Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs; 1 Web sites
  - Her Campus at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000607; Her Campus Media; 1 Web sites
  - Her Campus Tufts - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000608; Her Campus Media; 1 Web sites
  - Home - TEN, 2020 December 16; UA203.000609; Textbook Exchange Network; TCU Senate Textbook Exchange; 1 Web sites
  - Home - Tufts Humanist Chaplaincy, 2020 December 16; UA203.000610; Tufts Humanist Chaplaincy; 1 Web sites
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers - Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000611; Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers; 1 Web sites
  - InterVarsity at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000612; InterVarsity at Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - J Street U - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000613; J Street U Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - J Street U Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000614; J Street U Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Jumbo Jugglers - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000615; Jumbo Jugglers; 1 Web sites
  - JumboCode - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000616; JumboCode; 1 Web sites
  - JumboSec, 2020 December 16; UA203.000617; 1 Web sites
  - JumboSec - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000618; JumboSec; 1 Web sites
  - JumboSec - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000619; JumboSec; 1 Web sites
  - JumboVote, 2020 December 16; UA203.000620; 1 Web sites
  - JumboVote - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000621; JumboVote; 1 Web sites
  - JumboVote - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000622; JumboVote; 1 Web sites
  - KDSAP at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000623; KDSAP at Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Ladies of Essence - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000624; The Ladies of Essence; 1 Web sites
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, 2020 November 15; UA203.000625; 1 Web sites
  - Leonard Carmichael Society - LCS - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000626; Leonard Carmichael Society; 1 Web sites
  - Leonard Carmichael Society - LCS - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000627; Leonard Carmichael Society; 1 Web sites
  - Local Bard's Players - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000628; Local Bard's Players; 1 Web sites
  - Lord Barnum's Players, 2020 November 15; UA203.000629; 1 Web sites
  - Major: Undecided Sketch Comedy - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000630; Major: Undecided; 1 Web sites
  - Melisma Magazine - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000631; Melisma Magazine; 1 Web sites
  - Melisma Magazine - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000632; Melisma Magazine; 1 Web sites
  - National Society of Black Engineers - Tufts Chapter - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000633; National Society of Black Engineers Chapter at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Nu Chapter of Latinas Promoviendo Comunidad/ Lambda Pi Chi Sorority, Inc. - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000634; Nu Chapter of Latinas Promoviendo Comunidad/ Lambda Pi Chi Sorority, Inc.; 1 Web sites
  - One for the World, 2020 December 16; UA203.000635; 1 Web sites
  - Pen, Paint, and Pretzels - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000636; Pen, Paint and Pretzels; 1 Web sites
  - Pen, Paint, and Pretzels (3Ps) | Home - Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000637; Pen, Paint and Pretzels; 1 Web sites
  - PERIOD @ Tufts - Instagram, 2020 -- 2021; UA203.000638; Period at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Period at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000639; Period at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Project Linus at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000640; Project Linus Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - PROJECT SHARE - Home, 2020 December 16; UA203.000641; Tufts Project SHARE; 1 Web sites
  - Project SHARE - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000642; Tufts Project SHARE; 1 Web sites
  - Protestant Student Association, 2020 November 15; UA203.000643; 1 Web sites
  - Public Harmony - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000644; Public Harmony; 1 Web sites
  - Public Health at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000645; Public Health at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Pulse - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000646; Tufts Pulse; 1 Web sites
  - ROTI and RUM - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000647; ROTI and RUM; 1 Web sites
  - Shir Appeal, 2020 November 15; UA203.000648; 1 Web sites
  - Sino-U.S Relations Group Engagement - Tufts SURGE, 2020 November 15; UA203.000649; Tufts Sino-US Relations Group Engagement; 1 Web sites
  - Sino-U.S. Relations Group Engagement (SURGE) - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000650; Sino-U.S. Relations Group Engagement (SURGE); 1 Web sites
  - SMFA Student Government Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000651; SMFA Student Government Association; 1 Web sites
  - Society of Physics Students | Department of Physics and Astronomy, 2020 December 16; UA203.000652; Society of Physics Students; 1 Web sites
  - Society of Women Engineers Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000653; Society of Women Engineers Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Student Advisory Board - Tufts University Art Galleries, 2020 December 16; UA203.000654; 1 Web sites
  - Students of Turkey - SOFT - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000655; Students of Turkey - SOFT; 1 Web sites
  - Sunrise Movement Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000656; Sunrise Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Sunrise Tufts, 2020 December 16; UA203.000657; 1 Web sites
  - Sunrise Tufts - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000658; Sunrise Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Taiwanese Association of Students at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000659; Taiwanese Association of Students at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - TASTE: Tufts After School Tutoring and Enrichment - Leonard Carmichael Society, 2020 December 16; UA203.000660; TASTE: Tufts After School Tutoring and Enrichment; Leonard Carmichael Society; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Judiciary - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000661; Tufts Community Union Judiciary; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Senate Textbook Exchange - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000662; TCU Senate Textbook Exchange; 1 Web sites
  - TEDxTufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000663; TEDxTufts; 1 Web sites
  - TEDxTufts - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000664; TEDxTufts; 1 Web sites
  - TFL Comedy - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000665; TFL Comedy; 1 Web sites
  - The Institute Sketch Comedy - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000666; The Institute Sketch Comedy; 1 Web sites
  - The Left Unity Project - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000667; The Left Unity Project; 1 Web sites
  - The Palmier Magazine, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000668; 1 Web sites
  - The Tufts Amalgamates - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000669; The Tufts Amalgamates; 1 Web sites
  - The Tufts Anime Brigade - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000670; Tufts Anime Brigade; 1 Web sites
  - The Tufts Daily - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000671; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - The Tufts Daily - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000672; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - The Xi Tau Chapter of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc. - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000673; The Xi Tau Chapter of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc.; 1 Web sites
  - The Zamboni - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000674; The Zamboni; 1 Web sites
  - The Zamboni - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000675; The Zamboni; 1 Web sites
  - Tisch Council for Philanthropic Leadership - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000676; Tisch Council for Philanthropic Leadership; 1 Web sites
  - Torn Ticket II - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000677; Torn Ticket II; 1 Web sites
  - TTF - Home, 2020 December 16; UA203.000678; Tufts Trading Fund; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts ACTION - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000679; Tufts ACTION; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts American Red Cross Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000680; Tufts American Red Cross Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts American Society of Mechanical Engineers | Home - Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000681; Tufts American Society of Mechanical Engineers; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Animal Aid - Leonard Carmichael Society, 2020 December 16; UA203.000682; Tufts Animal Aid; Leonard Carmichael Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Armenian Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000683; Tufts Armenian Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts ASE Graduate Student Council - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000684; Tufts Graduate Student Council; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts ASE Graduate Student Council - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000685; Tufts Graduate Student Council; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts BEATs - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000686; BEATS; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Bhangra - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000687; Tufts Bhangra; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Bikes - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000688; Tufts Bikes; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Biology Research Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000689; Tufts Biology Research Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Biomedical Engineering Society - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000690; Tufts Biomedical Engineering Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Buddhist Mindfulness Sangha - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000691; Tufts Buddhist Mindfulness Sangha; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Calligraphy Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000692; Tufts Calligraphy Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts' Caribbean Students Organization - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000693; Tufts Caribbean Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Cheap Sox - Instagram, 2020 -- 2021; UA203.000694; Cheap Sox; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Cheerleading - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000695; Tufts Cheerleading; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts China Care Club, 2020 December 16; UA203.000696; Tufts China Care; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts China Care Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000697; Tufts China Care; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts CIVIC - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000698; Tufts CIVIC; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Consulting Collective - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000699; Tufts Consulting Collective; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Democrats, 2020 November 15; UA203.000700; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Democrats - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000701; Tufts Democrats; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts DREAM Mentorship Program - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000702; Tufts DREAM Mentorship Program; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Ears for Peers - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000703; Ears for Peers; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Electric Racing - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000704; Tufts Electric Racing; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Energy Group - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000705; Tufts Energy Group; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Entrepreneurs Society - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000706; Tufts Entrepreneurs Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Equestrian - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000707; Tufts Equestrian Team; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Eritrean-Ethiopian Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000708; Tufts Eritrean-Ethiopian Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Ewo - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000709; Tufts Ewo; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Ewo - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000710; Tufts Ewo; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Filipinx Student Union - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000711; Tufts Filipinx Student Union; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Financial Group, 2020 November 15; UA203.000712; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Food Rescue Collaborative - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000713; Tufts Food Rescue Collaborative; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Habitat For Humanity - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000714; Tufts Habitat For Humanity; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Hillel, 2020 November 15; UA203.000715; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Hillel - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000716; Tufts Hillel; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Hindu Students Council, 2020 November 15; UA203.000717; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Hindu Students Council - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000718; Tufts Hindu Students Council; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Historical Review - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000719; Tufts Historical Review; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Historical Review - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000720; Tufts Historical Review; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Hong Kong Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000721; Tufts Hong Kong Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts IGC - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000722; Tufts Inter-Greek Council; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Italian Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000723; Tufts Italian Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Jackson Jills - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000724; Tufts Jackson Jills; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Jackson Jills - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000725; Tufts Jackson Jills; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts JumboCast - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000726; Tufts JumboCast; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts JumboCode - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000727; Tufts JumboCode; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts JumboRaas - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000728; Tufts JumboRaas; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Korean Students Association - KSA - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000729; Tufts Korean Students Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Latin American Committee - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000732; Tufts Latin American Committee; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Math Society - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000733; Tufts Math Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Men's Ultimate - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000734; Tufts Men's Ultimate Frisbee; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Middle Eastern Dance - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000735; Tufts Middle Eastern Dance; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Minority Association of Pre-Health Students, 2020 November 15; UA203.000736; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mock Trial, 2020 November 15; UA203.000737; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mock Trial - Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000738; Tufts Mock Trial; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mock Trial - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000739; Tufts Mock Trial; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Model United Nations - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000740; Tufts Model United Nations; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts' Most Magical A Cappella Group - Tufts Enchanted, 2020 December 16; UA203.000741; Tufts Enchanted a capella; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mountain Club - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000742; Tufts Mountain Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts MSA - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000743; Tufts MSA a capella; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Muslim Students Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000744; Tufts Muslim Students Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts NeuroNetwork - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000745; Tufts Neuronetwork; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Observer - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000746; Tufts Observer; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Observer - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000747; Tufts Observer; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Pan Afrikan Alliance - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000748; Tufts Pan Afrikan Alliance; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Panhellenic Council, 2020 December 16; UA203.000749; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Panhellenic Council - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000750; Tufts Panhellenic Council; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Parnassus - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000751; Tufts Parnassus; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Parnassus - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000752; Tufts Parnassus; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Persian Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000753; Tufts Persian Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Premedical Society - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000754; Tufts Premedical Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Protestant Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000755; Tufts Protestant Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Psych Society - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000756; Tufts Psychology Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Quidditch, 2020 December 16; UA203.000757; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Quidditch - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000758; Tufts Quidditch; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Quidditch - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000759; Tufts Quidditch; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Relay for Life - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000760; Tufts Relay for Life; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Russian and Slavic Student Association, 2020 November 15; UA203.000761; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts S.O.L.E.S. – Society of Latinx Engineers and Scientists, 2020 December 16; UA203.000762; Tufts Society of Latinx Engineers and Scientists; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SEA - Instagram, 2020 -- 2021; UA203.000763; Tufts SEA; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SEDS - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000764; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SEDS - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000765; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts' S-Factor - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000766; Tufts' S-Factor; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Singapore, Indonesia, and Malaysia Students Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000767; Tufts Singapore, Indonesia, and Malaysia Students Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SJP - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000768; Tufts Students for Justice in Palestine; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SOLES - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000769; Tufts Society of Latinx Engineers and Scientists; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts South Asian Regional Committee - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000770; Tufts South Asian Regional Committee; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts sQ! - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000771; Tufts sQ!; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Strong Women, Strong Girls - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000772; Tufts Strong Women, Strong Girls; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Student Garden - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000773; Tufts Student Garden; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Student Services | Councils | Inter-Greek Council, 2020 December 16; UA203.000774; Tufts Inter-Greek Council; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Students for Justice in Palestine, 2020 November 15; UA203.000775; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Tamasha - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000776; Tufts Tamasha; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Tap Ensemble - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000777; Tufts Tap Ensemble; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Teach-In CORES - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000778; Tufts Teach-In CORES; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Thai Students Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000779; Tufts Thai Students Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Theta - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000780; Tufts Theta Chi, Epsilon Theta Chapter; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Timmy Global Health - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000781; Tufts Timmy Global Health; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Trading Fund - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000782; Tufts Trading Fund; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Traveling Treasure Trunk - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000783; Tufts Traveling Treasure Trunk; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts TURBO - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000784; Tufts TURBO; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Tutoring, 2020 November 15; UA203.000785; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Unitarian Universalists - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000786; Tufts Unitarian Universalists; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts United for Immigrant Justice - Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000787; Tufts United for Immigrant Justice; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Black Students in Computer Science - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000788; Tufts University Black Students in Computer Science; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Cricket Club, 2020 December 16; UA203.000789; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University History Society - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000790; Tufts History Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University History Society - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000791; Tufts University History Society; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Prison Initiative - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000792; Tufts University Prison Initiative of Tisch College; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Prison Initiative of Tisch College | Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life, 2020 December 16; UA203.000793; Tufts University Prison Initiative of Tisch College; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Republicans - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000794; Tufts University Republicans; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Television (TUTV) - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000795; Tufts University Television; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Vietnamese Students Club, 2020 November 15; UA203.000796; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Vietnamese Students Club (VSC) - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000797; Tufts Vietnamese Students Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Women in Computer Science - Home| Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000798; Tufts Women in Computer Science; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Women's Lacrosse - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000799; Tufts Women's Lacrosse; 1 Web sites
  - TUSC: Tufts University Social Collective - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000800; Tufts University Social Collective; 1 Web sites
  - WiCS - Women in Computer Science, 2020 November 15; UA203.000801; Tufts Women in Computer Science; 1 Web sites
  - Women Entrepreneurs at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000802; Women Entrepreneurs at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Women in International Relations at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000803; Women in International Relations at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Women's Higher Education Now - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000804; Women's Higher Education Now; 1 Web sites
  - Xi Tau Chapter of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, 2020 November 15; UA203.000805; The Xi Tau Chapter of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc.; 1 Web sites
  - Zeta Beta Tau - Instagram, 2020 -- 2021; UA203.000806; Zeta Beta Tau at Tufts; 1 Web sites
- Thinwire sites web crawls, 2011; UA203.000467; 51 Web sites
  A collection of 51 websites crawled by DCA to capture Tufts Univeristy websites on the Thinwire platform before the university moved to a different platform. Many of the websites captured in this collection are also described in the Tufts University web crawls series in their more recent iterations. The websites in this series were crawled on an one-time basis.
  - Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy - Giving & Alumni Relations, 2011-11-23; UA203.000468; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Catering, 2011-11-23; UA203.000469; 1 Web sites
  - Corporate and Foundation Relations, 2011-11-23; UA203.000470; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts China - Tufts University, 2011-11-23; UA203.000471; 1 Web sites
  - Commencement 2012 - School of Arts & Sciences and School of Engineering Commencement, 2011-11-23; UA203.000472; 1 Web sites
  - Medical and Sackler Commencement, 2011-11-23; UA203.000473; 1 Web sites
  - Department of Construction Management, 2011-11-23; UA203.000474; 1 Web sites
  - About the University-wide Committee on Ethics - Ethics Committee, 2011-11-23; UA203.000475; 1 Web sites
  - Accounts Payable, 2011-11-23; UA203.000476; 1 Web sites
  - Finance & Planning - Budget & Accounting, 2011-11-23; UA203.000477; 1 Web sites
  - Bursar, 2011-11-23; UA203.000478; 1 Web sites
  - Financial Information Systems, 2011-11-23; UA203.000479; 1 Web sites
  - Purchasing Office at Tufts University, 2011-11-23; UA203.000480; 1 Web sites
  - Risk Management & Insurance, 2011-11-23; UA203.000481; 1 Web sites
  - Sponsored Programs Accounting, 2011-11-23; UA203.000482; 1 Web sites